Past meets future.
The Adam Project is a adventure, science fiction,
comedy film directed by Shawn Levy.
After accidentally crash-landing in 2022, time-traveling fighter pilot Adam Reed
teams up with his 12-year-old self on a mission to save the future.
Big Adam, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Young Adam, played by Walker Scobell.
Louis Reed, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Ellie Reed, played by Jennifer Garner.
Laura, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Maya Sorian, played by Catherine Keener.
The Adam Project is a 2022 American science fiction action film
directed by Shawn Levy and written by Jonathan Tropper, T.
Nowlin, Jennifer Flackett, and Mark Levin.
The film stars Ryan Reynolds, Walker Scobell in his film debut, Mark
Ruffalo, Jennifer Garner, Catherine Keener, and Zoe Saldaña.
Reynolds plays the title character, a fighter pilot who steals a time jet and lands in 2022, encountering his 12-year-old self (Scobell), who had been dealing with the loss of his father
(Ruffalo) the year before, and must work together to prevent the assassination of his wife (Saldaña) and stop the leader from his timeline (Keener) from monopolizing time travel.
Production on the film first began in 2012 with Tom Cruise attached to star.
The film then fell into development hell until
Netflix acquired the distribution rights.
Filming commenced in November 2020 and wrapped in March 2021.
Rob Simonsen composed the score.
The Adam Project began a limited "one night only" theatrical release on
March 9, 2022, followed by its streaming release on March 11.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the performances, action sequences, visual
effects, and its inspiration from 1980s movies, but criticized its writing and storyline.
The film ranks as the third most popular movie on Netflix worldwide,
accumulating 157.6 million views in its first 28 days.
The film explores themes of escape, time travel, playful, explore, 2050s.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.